ratefinder.in 2010-12-26

# Travelocity India: Airfares, hotels, activities, cruises and more

## Privacy Policy  
8 November 2010

## Contents

  * Who we are.
  * ZUJI protects your privacy.
  * What information is collected and how do we use it?
  * Who do we share your information with?
  * You have control over your information!

## Who we are

Travelocity.com Private Limited ("Travelocity India") is a wholly owned subsidiary of ZUJI Pte Limited ("ZUJI") and operates its website located at www.travelocity.co.in using this Privacy Policy. All references to ZUJI shall be deemed to refer to Travelocity.com Private Limited, where appropriate.

Please note that this Privacy Policy will apply to your use of the Websites (as defined below) and the booking of travel thereon.

ZUJI is a leading online travel company in Asia Pacific offering a full suite of travel products and services (air tickets, accommodation, car rental) in the Asia-Pacific region. ZUJI’s head office is located at 67 Ubi Avenue 1, #06-12 Starhub Green, Singapore 408942. Tel: +65 6215 9600 Fax: +65 6215 9605.

ZUJI Pte Ltd is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This Privacy Policy covers the sites ([www.zuji.com.sg](http://www.zuji.com.sg/), [www.zuji.com.au](http://www.zuji.com.au/), [www.zuji.com.hk](http://www.zuji.com.hk/), [www.travelocity.co.in](http://www.travelocity.co.in/), [www.travelguru.com](http://www.travelguru.com/)) (collectively referred to herein as "our Websites"). ZUJI wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact: [Customercare_au@zuji.com](mailto:Customercare_au@zuji.com) for Australia, [Customercare_sg@zuji.com](mailto:Customercare_sg@zuji.com) for Singapore, [Customercare_hk@zuji.com](mailto:Customercare_hk@zuji.com) for Hong Kong, [Customercare@travelocity.co.in](mailto:Customercare@travelocity.co.in) for Travelocity India or [service@travelguru.com](mailto:service@travelguru.com) for TravelGuru. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe at <http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php>. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with ZUJI to resolve your concerns.

Back to Top

## ZUJI protects your privacy

ZUJI is committed to protecting your privacy in accordance with the highest consumer protection standards.

Our Privacy Policy is designed with you in mind, and it is integral that you have a comprehensive understanding of our Personal Information collection and usage practices, as well as full confidence that ultimately, you have control of your Personal Information provided to ZUJI. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, "Personal Information" shall mean any information that can be linked to a specific individual including without limitation, information such as name, address, telephone number, e-mail address and credit card number.

By using our Websites, you are deemed to have read, acknowledged and accepted all the provisions stated herein this Privacy Policy, including any changes that we may make from time to time.

In summary, while you should read each provision in this Privacy Policy, you note that by using our Websites:

  1. You agree that if you disclose your Personal Information to us, we may create a database record about you; 
  2. If you register on our Websites, download any materials or conduct any other transaction, you agree for us to collect any Personal Information necessary to provide you with the service you have requested, and you agree that such Personal Information may be disclosed to service partners (who may be third parties) for those purposes;
  3. You agree for us to use cookies on your browser (unless you remove them);
  4. You agree that we can contact you with information about products and services which may be of interest to you (unless you have stated you do not wish to receive these communications); and
  5. Your continued use of our Websites indicates your agreement with any future changes in this Privacy Policy.

Back to Top

## What information is collected and how do we use it?

ZUJI will not collect or monitor any Personal Information about you without your consent. The only Personal Information we collect is what you tell us about yourself and information about how you use our Websites. ZUJI collects information from you at several different points on our Websites:

**1\. New Member Registration**

  1. What information is collected? 

When you register as a member with ZUJI on our Websites, you will be asked to create a login name and password, as well as to provide your contact information, such as your name, title, email address, language preference and country of residence. You are also given the option to opt out from receiving periodical updates and/or newsletters from ZUJI informing you of the latest news and deals.

  2. Why do we collect it? 

We collect the above information for the following purposes:

    * To identify you when you use our Websites in order to enjoy a customized and personalised experience.
    * As a security measure, to send you an email confirming your membership registration.
    * To allow us to process and complete your travel reservations and purchases.
    * To send you email confirmations for your reservations and purchases on ZUJI.
    * For our customer service agents to contact you when necessary.
    * To send you our optional periodical updates and/or newsletters, if you have signed up for them.
    * To send you information about products and services which may be of interest to you.

**2\. Existing Member Travel Profile**  

  1. What information is collected? 

After registering as a member with ZUJI on our Websites, you are given the option to create a travel profile name and email address and to provide ZUJI with the following member travel profile information:

    * Credit card billing information, such as your credit card type, number, expiry date and billing address.
    * Ticket delivery information including telephone numbers and address details.
    * Passport information including passport number, place of passport issuance, passport issue date and passport expiration date.
    * Date of birth.
    * Travel preferences, such as preferred cities, date/time display preferences, flight seating and meal preferences, as well as others like frequent flyer numbers.
  2. Why do we collect it? 
    * With your member travel profile stored in ZUJI, you will enjoy convenience whenever you make travel reservations as you will not have to type the billing and delivery information repeatedly.
    * Your travel preferences will allow you to customize your experience on ZUJI, for example, in some circumstances, ZUJI will display your local currency.
    * To further confirm your identity.
    * To prevent credit card fraud.
    * To send you information about products and services which may be of interest to you.

**3\. My ZUJI**  

  1. What information is collected? 
    * Any time you make a purchased reservation, on hold reservation or save an itinerary while planning your trip on our Websites, your purchased reservation, on hold reservation or saved itinerary details will be saved into "My ZUJI".
  2. Why do we collect it? 
    * For your convenience, ZUJI stores your purchased reservation, on hold reservation or saved itinerary information in "My ZUJI", so that you may easily refer to your trip plans or complete your purchase. You are able to search your reservations using your Trip ID.
    * To send you information about products and services which may be of interest to you.

**4\. Online Surveys**  

  1. What information is collected? 
    * From time to time, ZUJI may employ the services of a third party to conduct market research surveys on our behalf. You may choose to participate in our surveys, and your answers to our survey, as well as your Personal Information may be kept on record, and will be protected in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. Please note that the Personal Information you provide through our surveys will be used on an aggregated basis unless we inform you otherwise beforehand.
  2. Why do we collect it? 
    * ZUJI conducts market research surveys in order to learn from you how improvements can be made to our Websites.
    * To send you information about products and services which may be of interest to you.

**5\. Customer Contact**  

  1. What information is collected? 
    * You may choose to provide feedback to ZUJI, for example through email or letters. The comments in your feedback, as well as your Personal Information, if provided to ZUJI, may be kept on record.
  2. Why do we collect it? 
    * The feedback that you choose to provide is valuable in helping ZUJI make improvements to our service to you. In order to follow-up on the feedback you have chosen to provide, ZUJI may correspond with you using the Personal Information that you have provided.

**6\. Cookies**  

  1. What information is collected? 
    * When you visit our Websites as a Guest or as a member, a cookie is stored onto your computer. A cookie is a small, encrypted text file containing some information about your preferences and allows your usage to be tracked. The use of cookies is now an industry standard, and you will find them used on most major websites. However, you can always choose to disable cookies from being stored on your computer by changing your browser settings. Disabling cookies, however, may result in a limited experience of our functionality and services and in some cases may mean that we are unable to provide you with the services, or parts of the services, that you have requested. Some of our business partners whose content is incorporated into or linked to from our Websites may also use cookies. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.
  2. Why do we collect it? 

Cookies, when stored on your computer, facilitate the following:

    * Cookies allow us to save encrypted passwords and preferences for you so that you will not have to re-enter them the next time you visit our Websites. This means you will be able to enjoy conveniences such as login without having to type your login name every time you visit ZUJI.
    * ZUJI will be able to make improvements to our Websites and customize your ZUJI experience using statistics collected from cookies. These statistics are anonymous to third parties, and may also be used by ZUJI's third party advertising companies, to monitor the effectiveness of advertisements.

**7\. Other Computer Information**  

  1. What information is collected? 
    * Session information such as IP (Internet Protocol) addresses, browser types, operating systems are also used for ZUJI's system administration.
  2. Why do we collect it? 
    * Session information will allow us to enhance your experience on ZUJI by allowing us to troubleshoot technical issues as well as to improve our Websites usability. It is also used to help prevent fraud or unauthorized use of our Websites.

**8\. Express Consent To Receive Pre-Recorded And Text Messages**  

  1. What information is collected? 
    * When you make a booking on our Websites, we will request you to provide us with a contact telephone number.
  2. Why do we collect it? 
    * We will use your telephone number in the event that we need to inform you of changes or other matters that may affect your booking or trip, such as changes due to flight delays, inclement weather, and cancellations. We may use an automatic telephone dialing system, artificial or prerecorded voice messages, or text messages to provide you with such updates. When you provide us with a cellular, wireless, or mobile telephone number as the contact number for a trip, you agree that you are providing us with your express consent to receive prerecorded voice messages or text messages related to your booking from ZUJI or any of our vendors or suppliers. If you do not wish to receive these trip updates on your cellular or mobile phone, please provide us with another telephone number.

Back to Top

## Who do we share your information with?

  1. ZUJI is the owner of all the Personal Information collected on our Websites. We do not sell or rent any Personal Information to third parties.
  2. In making a travel booking on our Websites, you may choose the option to send your itinerary to a friend, in which case an email with your trip details, such as hotel information, is sent to the email address that you specify. Your friend's email address will be used solely for the purpose specified above.
  3. We may disclose your Personal Information on occasion to third parties. Some of these third parties may be located outside your home country. For example, such countries may include, without limitation Singapore, Malaysia, Australia, New Zealand, Hong Kong, Taiwan Brunei and the US. The Personal Information will be protected in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. Disclosure may include without limitation, the following scenarios: 
    1. To successfully complete your travel reservations or purchases or otherwise implement our terms of service, your Personal Information is provided as needed to third party product and service providers and distributors including without limitation the airlines, hotels, car rental agencies, travel insurance agencies or other third parties authorised by ZUJI, whenever you purchase or reserve travel with ZUJI.
    2. When third parties have been authorised by ZUJI to perform projects such as market research surveys on our behalf or to offer you additional products and services.
    3. When required by law to disclose the Personal Information.
    4. With your prior express consent.
    5. To protect the rights and property of ZUJI.
  4. ZUJI may share your Personal Information with third parties when you engage in certain activities on our Websites that are sponsored by third parties, such as electing to receive information or communications from a third party (such as a hotel company or a tourism board for a particular destination), or electing to participate in promotions, contests, sweepstakes, games or other programs sponsored in whole or in part by a third party. ZUJI may also share your Personal Information when you respond to promotional materials from ZUJI and authorize a third party to use your Personal Information for purposes such as, for example, sending you additional promotional materials, providing you a product or service, or entering you in a contest, sweepstakes or game. We refer to all of these activities and requests as "Sponsored Activities." When you participate in Sponsored Activities, you will either be required or requested to agree that ZUJI may send your Personal Information (such as, in some cases, your mailing address or e-mail address) to the sponsor, and the sponsor may use your Personal Information in accordance with the sponsor's privacy practices. **In each case described in this section, ZUJI will only share your Personal Information after receiving your consent.** You should know that when ZUJI shares your Personal Information with a third party under any circumstance described in this section, your Personal Information will become permanently subject to the information use and sharing practices of the third party, and the third party will not be restricted by ZUJI's Privacy Policy with respect to its use and further sharing of your Personal Information.
  5. Links may be present on our Websites which result in you leaving our Websites and being taken to other third party websites. You should note that any Personal Information that you provide to these third party websites are not subject to this Privacy Policy, and we strongly recommend that you be aware of their respective privacy and security policies.
  6. ZUJI may also work with third parties that serve advertisements to our Websites. Information that may be disclosed to such third parties will be anonymous.
  7. You should also note that the processing of Personal Information on our Websites and the transmission of transaction messages relating to your travel reservations or purchases, including your Personal Information, may involve transmissions over various networks (which may not be secure) and to various countries (including the US) and further processing and storage of data in such countries.
  8. We may also disclose your Personal Information to our affiliates and non-affiliated business partners for their use both on our behalf and for their own business purposes. For example, our affiliates and business partners may use such Personal Information to send you information about their products, services, other information, and materials that may be of interest to you.
  9. To effect a corporate transaction, in connection with the sale, merger, acquisition, spin-off, or other corporate reorganization of our corporation, where your Personal Information may be disclosed, shared or transferred to the new controlling entity or other such authorised third party in the regular course of business.

Back to Top

## You have control over your information!

  1. Opt In and Opt Out Policy 
    * While ZUJI hopes that you benefit from our product and service offers, at any time, you always have the option to opt out from participating in ZUJI's product and service offers. For example, you will be given the option to unsubscribe to newsletters by unchecking the respective box. Please allow some time for this request to be processed.
    * We also offer you the ability to opt out of receiving information of our products and services, by accessing and changing your Personal Information or by sending an e-mail to us at [unsubscribe@zuji.com](mailto:unsubscribe@zuji.com). Please allow some time for this request to be processed.
    * If you do not want us to use your Personal Information or to share your Personal Information with third parties that are ZUJI's partners, please e-mail us at [privacy@zuji.com](mailto:privacy@zuji.com). Please allow some time for this request to be processed.
    * If you decide that you do not want ZUJI to use your Personal Information or to share your Personal Information with third parties, you understand and accept that this may in some cases impact on the availability of services and the quality of services that ZUJI may provide to you and may mean that the services provided to you (if possible at all) by ZUJI may not be customised for your use, may be less user- friendly and less efficient.
  2. Accessing your Personal Information and retention of Personal Information 
    * You may at any time access and change your Personal Information or subscribed services. You can easily access your Personal Information if you login as a member to ZUJI or you can follow the links that may be provided within our subscription emails to you to manage your subscription preferences. Although we will take reasonable steps to keep your Personal Information accurate, complete and up-to-date, we request that you keep your Personal Information as current as possible so that we may continue to improve our service to you.
    * We will only withhold your access to the Personal Information in limited circumstances where it is permitted by law, such as: 
      1. where it might be dangerous if you were to have it;
      2. where it might prejudice an investigation currently underway;
      3. where it relates to court proceedings and may be subject to the discovery process;
      4. where it may relate to a commercially sensitive decision-making process; or
      5. where other individuals' Personal Information is contained in the same record.
    * You agree that ZUJI may retain your Personal Information for a period of seven (7) years from the date you last accessed your account.
  3. Minors 
    * As we cannot distinguish the age of persons who access our Websites, a blanket privacy policy is applied. ZUJI does not seek or intend to seek to receive any Personal Information from minors (i.e. children younger than thirteen years of age). Should a parent or guardian have reason to believe that a minor has provided ZUJI with Personal Information without their prior consent, please contact us to ensure that the Personal Information is removed and unsubscribe them from any promotional contact opportunities.
  4. Tell-A-Friend 
    * If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our Websites, we will ask you for your friend's Personal Information including without limitation, name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit our Websites. ZUJI stores such Personal Information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.
  5. Security 
    * ZUJI has implemented technology and security features to safeguard the privacy of your Personal Information. A secure server protects your Personal Information. Additionally you can be assured that the information you provide to ZUJI is transmitted using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption. If you become aware of any security breach, please let us know as soon as possible.
    * We have internal procedures in place requiring our employees and data processors to respect the confidentiality of any Personal Information held by ZUJI.
    * ZUJI will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to keep secure any Personal Information which we hold about you. Your Personal Information is stored on secure servers that are protected in controlled facilities. Unfortunately, despite the aforementioned technology and security features, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, so we cannot give an absolute assurance that the Personal Information you provide to us will be secure at all times, and we cannot be responsible for any event arising from unauthorised access to your Personal Information. ZUJI will not be held responsible for events arising from third parties gaining unauthorized access to your Personal Information.
    * Please note also that ZUJI may use overseas facilities to process or back up your Personal Information. As a result, we may transfer to and store your Personal Information at our overseas facilities. However, this does not change any of our commitments to safeguard your privacy in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
  6. Keep your password safe 
    * You can play your part in safeguarding your Personal Information by never disclosing your login password or account information to anybody unless such person is duly authorized by you. Whenever you login as a member on ZUJI, particularly on somebody else's computer or on public internet terminals, you should always logout at the end of your session. Your assistance will help us protect the privacy of your Personal Information.
    * ZUJI cannot be held responsible for lapses in security caused by third party accesses to your Personal Information as a result of your failure to keep your Personal Information private. Notwithstanding the foregoing, you must notify us immediately if there is any unauthorised use of your account by any other internet user or any other breach of security.
  7. Contact us 
    * If you have any queries regarding our Privacy Policy, or should you have reason to believe that a breach of privacy has occurred, please submit your concerns to [privacy@zuji.com](mailto:privacy@zuji.com) or in writing to 67 Ubi Avenue 1, #06-12 Starhub Green, Singapore 408942. 
  8. Changes to the ZUJI Privacy Policy 
    * ZUJI may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in any way we use your Personal Information, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our Websites or by way of an e-mail and you will have a choice as to whether or not we may use the Personal Information in this different manner.

Thank you for taking the time to understand our Privacy Policy.

Back to Top
